autorecruitingplatform.com 2016-12-15

# Privacy Policy

QUICKLISTER™ PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy describes how we collect and use personal and other specific information that is obtained in connection with your access to this Website and the Software Services provided by QUICKLISTER.COM (the “Company”) through subscription to this Website and the Software Services (individually and collectively the “Services”). 

If you do not agree with any terms of this Privacy Policy please do not use the Services. By accessing any part of the Services, you agree to be bound by and have accepted this Privacy Policy in full. If you have any queries relating to this Privacy Policy, please contact us. 

1\. SCOPE

1.1 This Privacy Policy concerns the collection and use of personal and other specific information that is collected through your access to the Services. We are committed to protecting privacy, and accordingly, we do not collect personally identifying information unless it is provided voluntarily and knowingly, and do not share any information with anyone outside of our Company other than described herein. You are under no obligation to provide us with this information, but without it we may not be able to take appropriate action regarding your use of the Services. 

2\. MINORS

2.1 If you are under 13 years old, you may not use the Services or provide any of your personal information. Those under 18 years of age must have a parents or guardians permission to use the Services. 

3\. TRUSTE PRIVACY PROGRAM

3.1 QUICKLISTER™ is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, nonprofit organization whose mission is to build users’ trust and confidence by promoting fair information practices. In demonstrating its commitment to your privacy, the Company has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. By displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, this Web site has agreed to notify you of: 

3.2 What personally identifiable information of yours (or third party personally identifiable information) is collected from you through the web site; 

3.2.1 The organization collecting the information; 

3.2.2 How the information is used; 

3.2.3 With whom the information may be shared; 

3.2.4 What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of the information; 

3.2.5 The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of information; and 

3.2.6 How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

3.2.7 If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy you should first contact our Privacy Advocate by texting 480-725-2028. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe at www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Company to resolve your concerns. 

4\. INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

4.1 We collect personally identifying information to give you access to the Services, to optimize your experience using the Services, to respond to a request, and, if applicable, for email communications and billing purposes. For such use, you may be required to provide your e-mail address and other personally-identifying information (such as your name, phone number or date of birth) as we may deem necessary under the circumstances. When you provide any personally identifying information, you acknowledge that you are knowingly and voluntarily providing us the information, and that all such information is accurate and up-to-date. 

4.2 We may use your IP address and other related information such as browser type, time zone settings, and operating system in order to grant you access to and otherwise administer Services. 

4.3 We collect certain usage information about our Services, such as the number and frequency of Users and/or Users' Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, which are automatically logged and are used by us and our partners to analyze user activity at an aggregate level, such as the number of visits and geographic optimization. This data is used only in the aggregate and does not include any personally identifying information. 

4.4 You have the right to access your information held by The Company and, where necessary, to have it amended. 

5\. INFORMATION SHARING

5.1 By entering in your information you will be included in our Lead Redistribution Program, and the Company shall have the full rights to redistribute, sell or lease your information. 

5.2 We may provide such information to third parties without your consent if we reasonably believe that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms and Conditions, including investigation of potential violations, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or our safety or the safety of our users or the public as required or permitted by law. 

5.3 In addition to other provisions set forth herein, we might share profile information in a personally identifiable manner (this does not apply if you access the Service via the Facebook App) and aggregate usage information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties in order to present to you more targeted advertising, products and services. 

5.4 By entering in your information you are agreeing to receive sms text messages from us promoting additional offers other than the one you originally opted into. 

5.5 BY ENTERING YOUR MOBILE NUMBER YOU UNDERSTAND THAT YOUR CELL PHONE PROVIDER MY CHARGE YOU FOR THE MESSAGES YOU SEND AND RECEIVE FROM AND TO US. NEITHER, THE COMPANY, NOR ITS AFFILIATES OR SUBSIDIARIES, OR ANY OF OUR OR THEIR RESPECTIVE DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, PARTNERS, REPRESENTATIVES OR AGENTS REPRESENT, CAN BE HELD RESPONSIBLE FOR THESE CHARGES. 

6\. SUBMISSION OF OTHERS' PERSONAL INFORMATION

6.1 From time to time we may ask you to provide personal details of friends or business associates so that the Company can send them details of the Services. Before providing such information, please ensure that you have obtained their consent to their personal data being used in this way. We will not use these details in any manner that is incompatible with this Privacy Policy. 

7\. DATA SECURITY

7.1 We use a variety of security measures including encryption and authentication to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of your personal information under our control. Registered accounts are secured by your created username and password, and we take precautions to insure that account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. 

7.2 E-mails you send us are not necessarily secure when they are transmitted. If your communication is sensitive or includes highly confidential information, you may want to provide it by post or via the telephone instead. However, credit card information should not be sent to us by fax, post or email as we only accept the use of encrypted online shopping carts for payments. 

We instruct our employees with access to your information that it is to be used only in adherence with the provisions set forth in this Privacy Policy and applicable laws. 

8\. CREDIT CARD INFORMATION

With respect to your credit card information, this information if ever collected is sent encrypted to a secure server only for payment processing. The information is then used solely to complete your purchase order. 

9\. COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS

9.1 Like many companies, we use "cookie" and/or "web beacon" technology. Cookies may tell us whether you have accessed the Services before and what material you have viewed. Web Beacons are tags that can monitor the behavior of a user accessing the Services. 

9.2 Each time a user accesses the Services, we store a temporary 'cookie' in the browser files of that subscriber's computer or mobile device. This cookie is used during your connection with the Services to allow you free access to the Services, and to use the Services without repeatedly requiring you to re-enter your user name and password. When you log off or leave the Services, the cookies file is automatically removed. 

9.3 The cookies do not provide us with any way to contact you. 

9.4 You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set -- each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences -- however, you may have to enable cookies from in order to use and access some of the Services. 

9.5 Information recorded through web beacons is used to report anonymous individual and/or aggregate information about our users. 

9.6 By using the website you accept the use of cookies in relation to your use of the Services. 

10\. OTHER INFORMATION YOU SUBMIT

10.1 If you provide us with information other than personally-identifying information, including suggestions about the Services, all such information shall be solely owed by The Company may be used, reproduced, modified, distributed and disclosed by us in any manner in our sole discretion, without paying compensation to you. 

10.2 If you voluntarily post public information to such sections of the Services as public forums, you understand and acknowledge that such information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications. 

11\. OPT OUT

11.1 In any instance in which you are subscribed to any communications from us, you can unsubscribe or cancel your account at any time by texting 480-725-2028 a short message with your user name and/or email address you have used to subscribe. 

12\. CHANGES IN PRIVACY POLICY

12.1 The Company reserves the right, at our sole discretion, to change this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revised terms. It is your responsibility to check periodically for any changes and your continuing to access the Services indicates your acceptance of any current Privacy Policy. 

13\. HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by texting 480-725-2028. 

14\. MISCELLANEOUS

14.1 This Privacy Policy constitutes the entire agreement between you and us with respect to this Privacy Policy. 

14.2 This Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Arizona, applicable therein, without regard to conflict of laws. You irrevocably consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts located in the City of Scottsdale in the State of Arizona in connection with any action arising out of or related to this Privacy Statement or their subject matter. You waive any objection based on lack of personal jurisdiction, place of residence, improper venue or forum non-convenience in any such action. 

14.3 If any court having competent jurisdiction holds any provision of this Privacy Statement invalid or unenforceable in any respect, such provision shall be enforced to the maximum extent permitted by law, and the remaining provisions of this Privacy Statement shall continue in full force and effect. No waiver of any provision of this Privacy Statement shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such provision or any other provision of this Privacy Statement.
